I can get in here all day.
I think they're kind of sold out.
True... true... dimention... layering blush.
Difficult name
I'm Luna Moriya from Sakurazaka 46.
Today, I've come here, to at Cosme Tokyo.
Oh, Jean.
I really like amazing cosmetics and stuff,
I usually search, collect, and buy cosmetics,
I often come here in my private life as well,
Today, I would like to take a look at the latest cosmetics.
I'd like to go inside.
Let's go!
Wow, it's huge! There are all kinds of cosmetics. Amazing!
First of all, when I come to this store in my private time, I always go into this round place.
I check it out a lot.
This is a very popular place.
It's the kind of product that, if you apply it to an area where you are worried about unevenness in color, it will make the area look better,
I've had a makeup artist use it, and it was really good.
I haven't changed it yet.
I haven't changed it yet, but I like all of them.
Oh, this one. I have this one.
It was talked about a lot, so I tried it,
It's like water, but it's not water.
It's not water, but it covers so lightly that you don't really need foundation,
It was great. It made me feel soft and smooth.
This one.
This one has been here for a long time.
I've used this mascara remover so much that I don't know how many I've bought.
I recommend it because removing mascara is so much easier just by using it like this.
Wow, that's great. Wait, what should I do? I'll get out for a minute.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
This way is the Depakos section.
Wow, cute. Wow.
Ah! This! Lior?
This blush, this glittery blush.
I hear it's really good.
It's so cute! It's a new one.
I heard you can open the drawer.
Oh, but do they have it? This color
212. 212.
Oh, my God, I wonder which one it is...
Looks like it's sold out.
Oops, no, but it looks popular.
I wonder if they're sold out
I hope so
Emusic Rush
Oh, I don't see it.
Uh-oh, it's not here. It was sold out. Too bad.
Too bad, it was sold out.
I was wondering about this!
Hince blush.
A makeup artist once used this color for me.
This, this.
It was so cute, this color.
I want it! But it's amazing!
It looks like it's selling really well!
Oh, there's only two boxes.
Is this it? The color.
I've always wanted one of these.
Dreamlike.Dreamlike
Dreamlike.
I have the last two items.
I got the Dreamlike!
Yay! I've always wanted one.
I tend to buy things that are used by makeup artists.
Basically, I tend to buy things that are used by makeup artists.
Oh, the pack zone!
I collect so many packs!
I want to try different kinds.
Uru-uru-ombombo-bubu
How do you read this?
"Lulu-lulu-bombu"? Bonbu?
I don't know how to read it.
It's kind of pink and cute.
But I can stay here all day.
It's too much fun.
This eyeshadow is kind of cute.
Maybe I'll try it on.
I guess it's easier to tell with this one for now.
Ooh! It's so cute!
Can you see the lame?
It's a little pinkish lame.
It's so cute!
Okay, I'll put this in the basket.
Pow! I put it in.
Yes!
I want an ensitalip.
It's so cute!
Let's try some on.
I'm having a hard time choosing a lipstick, aren't you?
I have so much trouble.
What should I do?
What did I put on just now?
Kaya Fig?
What? What?
Kaya Fig? You painted this?
Oh, you painted this. Yes, I did. Well, I'm going to buy some of this. I've been curious about it.
Oh, I'd like to talk to the sales clerk.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Do you have any recommendations in all genres?
Yes, I do.
Yes, please.
I think you should definitely buy it, so I bought this sheet.
Oh, I see.
It's from a famous brand called Lulurun,
It's called "Type Sensory Sheet," and when you take it out, it stretches like crazy.
Wow, that's amazing.
When you put them out, they grow very fast.
I'll take this now.
Thank you very much.
I was wondering if there is anything that you would like to highlight?
I was curious about it.
It's called "Blush UV," and if you spread it on like this, you can see a hint of color.
Really. Wow, that's amazing.
It's hard to imagine what the coloring is like now.
Indeed. It's blending in. It's amazing.
Yes, it is.
It's nice. I want one.It's nice. I want it.
Maybe I'll buy it. I didn't know such a thing existed when I heard about it.
Oh, really? I'm glad.
I'd like to unpack what I bought.
First, the pack you recommended.
It looks really good, doesn't it?
Seven vitamins and seven herbs for intensive care.
Also, I'm really interested in these stretchy sheets.
I can't wait to use it!
Next
True Dimension Layering Cheek
What a difficult name!
This is the blush I've been wanting so badly!
Hince blush
Yay!
It's such a very, very pretty color!
Where do I use this purple?
Apply a thin layer on the high cheeks.
Wow! I didn't know that's how you use it.
I brought a brush, so I'll apply it on my cheeks.
Two pieces.
Did you see the change?
Pretty color.
Next time...
I think I'll try this one.
This is Ailey's
Chrono Beauty Color On UV Blush 01
It's an amazing cream.
Oh, it smells so good.
Oh, it smells great.
Oh, I don't know...I didn't know
But I'm looking forward to applying this one soon. Very much.
Okay, then.
Let's try this one.
Bare Eyeshadow Palette #04, Ruikku.
Ta-da!
So cute!
The lame is so cute.
Cute, cute, cute.
Like this.
I can't wait to use this one too! It's so cute!
The last one!
Ta-da!
This is a lip!
Rom & Team
Melting Arm
This is what the color looks like
Let's apply it.
Oh! It's so pretty and luscious.
I love luscious lips.
It doesn't seem to dry out.
Next, I'd like to show you what's in the pouch I always bring with me.
My Melo!
I'm a little embarrassed to say that this is just a normal lipstick that I use.
The colors are really good here, too.
It's just the right amount of lube, and it's really cute!
I like mascara a lot, and I often get compliments on my eyelashes.
I used this again today.
Kingdom Curl Mascara
First, I applied it in this fine line.
Then, use this thicker part to curl the base of your lashes.Then, if you take this thicker part and grind it around the base of the lashes...
You can get beautiful fine lashes with this thicker part.
I bought it recently and it's my favorite!
Eyeliner
This creamy touch eyeliner from Cammake.
I forgot to do this.
I wanted to do this.
This is it.
When I lift up my eyelashes, I'm worried about my mucous membrane.
So I just put it on the mucous membrane.
There were three lipsticks in the package.
They are so cute!
They are Korean cosmetics.
The round shape is so cute!
The color is also really cute, so I use it.
I'm also using this color called Pink Fondue from Lilimu.
It's also really cute and I've been using it a lot lately.
And lastly, to make my mouth a little more luminous.
I use this Jill Stuart color.
I can't see it because of my eyesight.
I use this color.
It makes my mouth look fuller and not dry all the time.
It also makes my mouth look more rounded.
It's like this.
That's the contents of the pouch.
This was my first time to shoot for YouTube.
It was a lot of fun!
I would like to do makeup videos if there are people who want to see them.
I would also like to cook and do other things with the members.
I really hope to have a lot of fun with the members again.
Thank you for watching until the end!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Bye bye!